seattlemet.com 2010-05-28

# Seattle Met Magazine / About Seattle Met / Privacy Policy

Main Content

_Effective January 12, 2009_

Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to protecting all users’ privacy in accordance with the following policies. The term “users” includes registered members of our website and non-registered visitors that access our web pages. Please carefully read our privacy policy as outlined below.

## About Seattlemet.com

SagaCity Media Inc owns and operates the Seattlemet.com website (hereby referred to as “SM.com” or “we”). Please contact us directly if you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies. We can be reached at:

623 SW Oak St, Ste 300  
Portland, OR 97210  
web@sagacitymedia.com

## Information collection and use

SM.com collects certain user-submitted information (“personal information”) so that users may operate various features of the SM.com website. Any user may access our website’s home page and browse our website without disclosing personal information. For website activities that request personal information, you agree to provide accurate and current information about yourself. We may retain personal information for an indefinite amount of time to preserve our database and to comply with various federal and state laws.

To participate as a member of the SM.com website or in online activities, you may be required to provide personally identifiable information such as your e-mail address and zip code. We collect personal information for several important purposes, including providing subscriber services, operating our membership base, protecting the security of our users and the website, improving or adding features to our service and website, or distributing our newsletters. A user’s e-mail address or zip code is not shared with or displayed to other users.

We also offer an “e-mail a friend” feature that allows members to share SM.com website content with others. We do not collect or store the sender or recipient’s e-mail information for this feature.

The only personal information the SM.com website obtains is information voluntarily provided by you through our website. This website does not collect additional personal information about individual users from other sources. To manage our website and improve our website services, we may collect non-personal information about our users, such as Internet server and browser identification, Internet service provider, clickstream information, the web page from which a person enters our site, web pages visited, duration of visit, domain type, IP address, member lists, and aggregate user data. This information does not reveal a user’s personal identity. This information, which is not personally identifiable, may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

## Information sharing and disclosure

SM.com will only share or disclose users’ personal information with companies other than SM.com when it is required by law; when disclosure is necessary to operate the website or certain website services; to protect the safety of our users, employees, or property; and/or when disclosure is consistent with SM.com’s practices for services that are similarly provided offline. The SM.com website may offer members the opportunity to discuss restaurants, bars, events, trails, or other items, or to participate in interactive areas. Your member name may appear next to your comments or other postings or participation in interactive areas on the website. Your member name may also appear on a member profile section of the website. We may also use and disclose your member name and reviews and ratings in any other manner in accordance with the Terms of Service Agreement.

SM.com may in the future share personal information with our parents, partners, affiliates, or other entities for other purposes. If we decide to enter into such sharing arrangements, we will disclose to our registered users and in this Privacy Policy the name of the entity(ies) that we will share information with, what type of personal information will be shared, how the information will be used, and how to contact us if you do not want us to share your personal information (“opt-out”). We may conduct joint activities with members of the SM.com family; however, we will not share individual users’ personal information with these entities unless we provide notice in this Privacy Policy.

When users send e-mail correspondence to us, we will protect your e-mail address and other personal contact information. We may share your personal information with our operational providers or those persons, companies, or agents who provide support for the internal operations of the website, such as maintenance and technical services.

SM.com may collect and provide aggregate information about our users to our advertisers, sponsors, promotional partners, and affiliates, such as how many persons visited a particular page or activity, or the likes and dislikes of our users, but this information does not include personal information about any individual user. We may obtain geographic information such as zip-code clustering from other sources, but this aggregate information will not reveal any personal information about a specific user.

## Information Collection and Use by Advertisers

SM.com uses a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our website. This advertising company may collect and use information (not including personally identifiable information) about your visits to our site and other websites not owned and operated by SM.com in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In addition, we may share non-personal website usage information about users to this website with this company for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements and for market research analysis on our site and other sites. In the course of serving advertisements to this website, our third party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your computer. If you would like more information about the collection, use and disclosure practices of this third party advertising company and to know your choices about not having this information used by this company, [click here](http://www.godengo.com/media/Godengo).

Our website may post banner ads and other forms of advertisements, and/or links to the websites of affiliate entities or of advertisers or sponsors, which are companies that are not owned or operated by SM.com, its parents, affiliates, or subsidiaries. These entities may independently solicit and collect personal information, or send their own cookies to our users. Please be advised that when you link to or visit an advertiser’s or sponsor’s website, you will be subject to the privacy policy and terms of usage agreement of that website operator. SM.com, its parents, affiliates, or subsidiaries will not be responsible for advertiser or sponsor ads and/or links, or the content, activities, information collection or use and disclosure practices of the websites of advertisers and sponsors.

## Cookies

The SM.com website uses cookies and/or other tracking devices. A cookie is a small data file that contains a unique identification number that a website places on your hard drive when you visit a site. The “cookie” is able to store information such as data about your computer, the type of browser you use, and how many times your computer visits a certain site. Cookies do not allow the website to access personal information that you haven’t already provided. Cookies enable us to track how often users are visiting our website and specific pages, the number of entries in specific events, the estimated audience size for sponsors and advertisers, and user preferences. You can refuse to use cookies by turning them off in your browser. Please contact your software manufacturer for questions on how to disable your cookies. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use most of our website. However, you may find that some areas on the website will be slower, or may not function at all, and you may not be able to participate in certain activities if the cookies are disabled. Our web advertising partners may set cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by SM.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Security

For the convenience of our users, SM.com may offer a list of helpful website links provided by other entities and/or persons. SM.com does not endorse or recommend, nor is it liable for, the products or services of any websites not owned or operated by SagaCity Media Inc. When you visit other websites you will also be subject to the privacy policies and terms of usage or service agreements, if any, of that website operator.

## Privacy policy changes

SM.com will review our security measures and Privacy Policy on a periodic basis, and we may modify our policies as SM.com deems appropriate. We may also change or update our Privacy Policy if we add new services or features, and we will post these changes in this policy. We will provide notification of such Privacy Policy changes for our website users.

Please contact us with any questions about the Privacy Policy for SM.com. Thank you for visiting Seattlemet.com.
